well if you have your notes in front of
好吧，如果你有你的笔记在前面
you turn it over to the section called
你把它转到所谓的部分
psychotropic drugs and biblical
精神药物和圣经
counseling how do we deal with that now
咨询我们现在 如何处理这个问题
you understand that especially if you
你明白，特别是如果你
come out of the medical field there's no
走出医疗领域就没有了
way in the world that we're going to be
我们将成为 世界的方式
able to exhaustively cover all the
能够详尽地涵盖所有
circumstances that could occur in
可能发生在情况
counseling in a short 50 minute time
在短短的50分钟内进行咨询
period but at least we want to give you
期间但至少我们想给你
an introduction and there's a lot that I
介绍 ，我有很多
do want to say that hopefully will be of
还是要说，希望它们的
help to you
帮助你
from a biblical perspective so let's get
从圣经的角度来看，让我们得到
into this and there's some of this
进入这个并且有一些这个
that's early part of my remarks that
这是我的言论早一部分
actually dr. Baker is going to cover in
实际上博士。贝克将要报道
a later session on physical issues in
以后关于体育问题的会议
the body and the human body and those
身体和人体以及那些
kind of things so I'm not going to spend
有点事情，所以我不打算花
a long time belaboring some of those
其中一些人很长一段时间
points because he's going to cover them
因为他要掩盖他们
much more thoroughly but we do want to
更彻底但我们确实想要
introduce them as part of the whole
将它们作为整体的一部分介绍
picture of mankind that's what we want
人类的照片， 这就是我们想要的
to do so if you want to pull your notes
如果你想拉笔记，这样做
out and get your Bibles ready that's
出来让你的圣经准备好了
what we want to do let's talk about what
我们想做什么让我们谈谈什么
the Bible has to say about physical
圣经必须说实物
issues physical and spiritual aspects of
问题的身体和精神方面
counseling is what we're really dealing
咨询是我们真正的交易
with and the Bible gives us reasons for
与圣经给我们理由
actual organic problems that is ailments
实际的有机问题是疾病
sicknesses those kind of things remember
这些事情记住了
how I said in an earlier session there
我早些时候在那里会谈过的
is no such thing as mental illness
不是精神疾病
mental ailment illness is an oxymoron
精神疾病是一种矛盾
it's like jumbo shrimp right or
它像大虾权利或
military-intelligence
军事情报
those kind of things a couple of terms
那些事情有几个术语
that don't go together
不一起去
I just alienated all the military people
我只是疏远了所有的军人
in the audience didn't I well I come out
在观众中我不是很好，我出来了
of the Air Force I was in the Air Force
空军的我空军
for six years so I know that I'm a part
六年，所以我知道我是其中的一员
of that so I guess I it qualifies me to
那我觉得我有资格参加
be able to say something but oxymorons
除了矛盾之外能说些什么
that that's that's mental illness now
这就是 现在 的精神疾病
there is such thing as actual physical
有实际的身体这样的东西
illness in fact Luke himself was a
事实上，卢克本身就是一个病
member of the disciples and he certainly
他当然是门徒
was a physician
是一名医生
and the Bible gives us reasons why there
圣经告诉我们为什么在那里
is sickness for example in Genesis
例如在创世记中就是疾病
chapter 3 Romans 5 Hebrews chapter 9
第3章罗马书5希伯来书第9章
verse 27 the reason why we live in a
第27节我们住在一个地方 的原因
world with sickness and ailment is
疾病和疾病的世界是
because we live in a sin cursed
因为我们生活在被诅咒的罪中
environment and death is now a part of
环境和死亡现在是其中的一部分
that environment originally man and
那个环境原本是男人和
woman was designed to live forever life
女子被设计为长生不老的生命
without end but then sin was introduced
没有结束但是罪被引入了
and actually death was a act of mercy by
实际上死亡是仁慈的行为通过
God because to live perpetually in a
上帝因为永远生活在一个
world of sin would have been hell and so
罪恶的世界将是地狱等
death becomes an actual act of mercy
死亡成为一种实际的怜悯行为
from God to bring our life to an end
来自上帝，使我们的生命结束
here and now to show you that there is a
这里和现在向您展示有一个
different way to live eternally in a
永远生活在一个不同的方式
sinless environment that's the way that
无罪的环境就是这样
God intended it from the very beginning
上帝从一开始就打算这样做
so Genesis 3 Romans 5 Hebrews 9:27 says
所以创世纪3罗马书5希伯来书9:27说
we live in a world of sickness because
我们生活在一个疾病的世界，因为
we live in a world of sin but we also
我们生活在一个充满罪恶的世界，但我们也是
know as well that their sin or sickness
也知道他们的罪恶或疾病
can be sin engendered we can see that in
可能是罪恶，我们可以看到
James chapter 5 verses 15 and 16 and
詹姆斯5章15和 16
some of this can be a part of the
一些本可以的一部分
natural consequences of sin for example
例如，罪的自然后果
of a person that misuses drugs over a
一个人滥用药物而不是一个人
period of time whether they're legal or
他们是合法还是合法的时间段
illegal drugs doesn't matter eventually
非法药物 最终无关紧要
those drugs misuse are gonna take a toll
那些滥用的药物会造成损失
on the physical body or there's an abuse
在身体上或有滥用
of alcohol and that person becomes a
酒精和那个人变成了
drunkard and eventually they suffer from
醉汉，最终他们受苦了
cirrhosis of the liver or you can
肝硬化还是可以的
internalize things that are going on in
内化正在进行的事情
your life strife stress all of that is
你的生活冲突压力都是如此
internalized and eventually you develop
内化，最终你发展
some sort of heart disease because of
某种心脏疾病的原因的
that all of that internalized stress all
所有内在的压力都是如此
of that has to do with unbiblical
这与不符合圣经的事情有关
responses to life someone has not
对生活的回应有人没有
helped you to know how to how to respond
帮助您了解如何回应
to those those difficult times in life
那些生活中的那些困难时期
that's that's hard so you can you can
这很难，所以你可以
drive dangerously because you're angry
因为你生气而危险地开车
sinfully angry down the freeway and get
在高速公路上愤怒地生气并得到
in an accident and now you suffer a
在一次事故中，你现在受苦了
broken leg or worse a broken pelvis and
断腿或骨盆坏了
then now you suffer from that for the
那么现在你为此受苦了
rest of your life there's going to be an
你的余生将会是一个
abnormality there that's a sin
那里的异常就是罪
engendered thing well also it can be a
主义及其件事做好也可以是一个
result of unbiblical responses like
不符合圣经的反应的结果
anger I used the illustration in one of
愤怒我使用的插图中的一个
our earlier session about the man in our
我们之前关于我们这个人的会议
church who had a real problem with anger
教会真的有愤怒的问题
and went around putting his fist through
并四处走动
the hollow-core doors in his house and
他家里的空心门
every single hollow core door in his
他的每一个空心门
heart house had a hole in it so anger
心脏屋有一个洞，所以愤怒
you you you hit a door and you break
你，你打门，你打破了
your hand or the bones in your hand or
你的手或手中的骨头或
your wrist you can internalize stress
你的手腕可以内化压力
and you can grit your teeth and you can
你可以咬紧牙关，你可以
begin over a period of time to have jaw
开始一段时间有下巴
pain and you do it until it becomes a
痛苦，你做到它直到它成为一个
habitual eyes thing in your life you
习惯性的眼睛的事情在你的生活你
actually train the muscles of your body
实际上训练你的身体肌肉
to do that and your muscles have a
要做到这一点，你的肌肉有一个
certain muscle memory to them so that
某些肌肉记忆给他们， 让
even it's in when you're sleep asleep or
即使是在你睡着或睡着的时候
unconscious you're actually gritting
无意识你实际上是在咬牙切齿
your teeth and you have jaw pain as a
你的牙齿和下颌疼痛
result of that which is a response to
的该结果是一个响应
the pressures that are going on in your
你们的压力正在发生
life you can habituate your body to all
生活中你可以习惯所有人的身体
kinds of things and your muscles grow
各种各样的东西和你的肌肉成长
use to those sinful and godly responses
用于那些有罪和敬虔的回应
to life if you ever go to the morgue and
生活如果你去太平间和
see a person before they've been
在他们去之前看一个人
embalmed that whatever muscle movements
无论肌肉运动如何，都要进行防腐
they've had in life they still have
他们在生活中仍然拥有
after they're dead their brain dead but
他们死了之后他们的大脑死了但是
their bodies still moving you can go to
他们的身体还在移动，你可以去
the morgue and see a pianist who has
太平间， 看到有钢琴家
been a pianist all their life and
他们一生都是钢琴家
they're laying there on the slab and
他们在平板躺在那儿和
their fingers are still doing
他们的手指还在做
all right why because of muscle memory
没错，为什么因为肌肉记忆
when I was a boy we had chickens at our
当我还是个男孩的时候，我们就养了鸡
house and we butchered chickens all
房子， 我们都屠杀了鸡
right what happens when you chop the
对你砍的时候会发生什么
head off of a chicken
从鸡身上掉下来
yeah runs around flapping it sweet how
是的，如何四处奔波
does it save a totally brainless chicken
它能拯救一只完全没脑子的鸡吗？
all right there's no brain whatsoever in
好吧，没有任何大脑
that chicken and they're still running
那只鸡，他们还在跑步
around the barnyard flapping its wings
在谷仓周围扇动翅膀
and running now how is that possible
现在运行的怎么可能
well because of muscle memories well you
因为你的肌肉记忆很好
have a physical body that you trained in
有一个你训练过的身体
a sinful way to and you you some of you
一个有罪的方式，你和你们中的一些人
have written a bike for years but when
多年来写了一辆自行车但是什么时候
you're a kid you learn how to ride a
你是个孩子， 你学习如何骑
bike if I brought a two-wheel bike in
如果我带一辆两轮自行车的话
Australia they call it a push bike if I
如果我，澳大利亚他们称之为自行车
brought a push bike in here and you got
在这里带了一辆自行车，你就得到了
on it you feel really awkward it's been
你觉得它真的很尴尬
50 years since I've ridden one of those
自从我骑过其中一个之后的 50年
things but pretty soon your muscles
事情， 但很快你的肌肉
remember how it went and pretty soon
记得它是如何去的很快
you're riding that bike and oh yeah I
你骑着那辆自行车哦，是的，我
remember this now I remember that
记住这一点，现在我还记得
because you trained your body in your
因为你 在训练的你的身体你的
body your muscles remember those
身体你的肌肉记住那些
particular movements well we habituate
特别的运动我们习惯了
our bodies to sin in the same way we do
我们的身体就像我们一样犯罪
exactly the same thing and sometimes
完全相同的事情，有时候
that has physiological consequences when
这会产生生理后果
we do that kind of thing so now I want
我们现在就做那样的事情
you to understand at this particular
你要明白这一点
point that God's purpose is more than
指出上帝的目的不止于此
just us getting well from that sickness
只是我们从这种疾病中恢复健康
God's purpose is more than just getting
上帝的目的不仅仅是获得
well that's really key let's go to on
那真是关键，让我们继续吧
the third thing I'm gonna come back and
我要去的第三件事回来
talk about that in a moment also we find
我们也会在一瞬间谈到这一点
out the Apostle Paul says in 2nd
使徒保罗在第二节说
Corinthians 12 that he had a for in the
哥林多前书12章，他曾参加过
flesh I know that there are many who
肉体我知道有很多人
interpret that to be an actual person
将其解释为真实的人
that was a problem in Paul's ministry
这是保罗事工中的一个问题
there is however many commentators who
然而，有许多评论员
believe that this was an actual physical
相信这是一个实际的身体
problem that Paul had and it's possible
保罗所遇到的问题，这是可能的
I've gone through that particular
我经历过那个特别的事
passage with a fine-tooth comb in the
用细齿梳子通过
original language and it can go either
原始语言，它可以去
way I tend to think because of the
这样， 我倾向于 认为由于
terminology that he used that it's
他用过的术语就是这样
actually a physical element but that's
实际上是一个物理元素，但那是
my only belief that's
我的唯一信念是
my conclusion if you no I don't think
我的结论如果你不，我不认为
that's a fundamental of face so if you
这是面子的基础所以如果你
stuck a gun to my head I'd deny it
把枪放在我头上我会否认它
so I'm not gonna hold on to it but I
所以我不会坚持下去，但我
tend to think that that's a physical
倾向于认为，这是一个物理
ailment and if that's the case then the
疾病，如果是这样，那么
Apostle Paul says it's it's he went to
使徒保罗说这是他去的
the Lord and asked of the Lord would
主并且要求主愿意
remove this thorn in the flesh and God
去除肉体和上帝的刺
kept coming back to him and saying my
一直回来给他，说我
grace is sufficient for you my strength
恩惠足以让你发挥我的力量
is made perfect in your weakness so why
由完美在你的弱点，为什么
why well because Paul said that he had
为什么好，因为保罗说他有
received such great revelation from God
从上帝那里得到了如此伟大的启示
he had a tendency it would feed his
他有一种倾向会养活他的
pride his sinful pride in his life and
在他的生命中骄傲自豪
it was that thorn in the flesh that kept
那是保持肉体的刺
him from becoming so prideful so
他成为如此如此自傲
prideful so Paul's thorn keeps him from
骄傲所以保罗的荆棘阻止了他
pride keeps him from exalting himself
骄傲使他不能高举自己
it keeps Paul humble and he as a result
它使保罗谦卑，结果他
has this attitude of humility and a
有这种谦卑的态度和
desire to see God's purposes being
渴望看到上帝的旨意
fulfilled through that sickness God's
通过那种疾病来实现上帝的
purposes again is more important than
目的再次比重要
just getting healed God's purposes are
刚刚得到医治上帝的目的是
more important than just getting healed
比愈合更重要
or there's another reason for sickness
还是有其他原因导致疾病
the glorification of God you remember in
你记得的上帝的荣耀
John chapter 9 this is the mourn man who
约翰·第9章，这是悲哀的人谁
was born blind and the disciples had the
天生失明，门徒有了
typical Jewish mentality that if a
典型的犹太心态，如果一个
person was born like that then either he
那个人就像他那样出生
sinned and they actually had a belief
犯了罪，他们实际上有一种信仰
system where a baby could sin in utero
婴儿可能在子宫内犯罪的系统
and God as a result of that would punish
而上帝因此而受到惩罚
them so here's a person born blind or
他们这是一个天生失明的人
either he sinned or his parents sinned
要么他犯了罪，要么他的父母犯了罪
well who sent the caused him to be born
谁送了谁导致他出生
blind and Jesus said neither but this
盲人和耶稣说不是这个
has happened so that God can glorify
已经发生，以便上帝可以荣耀
himself through the healing of that
他自己通过愈合
sickness and jesus heals him so God's
疾病和耶稣治愈他，所以上帝的
purpose and glory is more than just
目的和荣耀不仅仅是
getting well getting over the illness is
越来越好地克服疾病了
not the primary goal the man born blind
不是盲人的主要目标
had an ailment not because of a sin
有一种疾病不是因为犯罪
but because God's glory might be
但因为上帝的荣耀可能是
displayed so getting over the illness
显示所以克服疾病
cannot be the primary goal in your life
不能成为你生活中的主要目标
when you become ill God can be glorified
当你生病时，上帝可以得到荣耀
number 1 through the healing that's
通过愈合的数字1
certainly possible or number 2 allowing
当然可能或2号允许
the sickness to remain or number 3 by
疾病留下或3号
taking the believer home God can still
把信徒带回家上帝仍然可以
be glorified in any one of those those
在那些人中得到荣耀
three ways so why do we where do we get
三种方式，为什么我们在哪里得到
sick physically well because we live in
身体不好因为我们住在这里
a world of sin sometimes we get sick
一个罪恶的世界，有时我们会生病
because it's stuff that we've done to
因为这是我们做过的事情
ourselves sometimes we're sick because
我们有时候因为生病而生病
it's keeping us from further sin and
它让我们远离罪恶
sometimes we're sick so that God can use
有时我们生病了， 所以上帝可以使用
our life to bring glory to him maybe
我们的生命也许给他带来荣耀
even through our deaths and a wonderful
即便通过我们的死亡和一个美好的
lady was part of our congregation
女士是我们会众的一部分
several years ago she was one of our
几年前她是我们的一员
Deaconess says and she her name was Sue
Deaconess 说，她的名字叫苏
Walters never forget sue sue eventually
沃尔特斯最终永远不会忘记起诉
died of breast cancer and I had the
我死于乳腺癌
privilege as their pastor to walk her
特权作为他们的牧师走她
into heaven house a great thing in the
进入天堂容纳在一个伟大的事情
last day of her life she's bleeding from
她的生活她从流血的最后一天
every orifice of her body her eyes her
她的每一个孔都是她的眼睛
nose her mouth her ears and we're
她的嘴巴，她的耳朵，我们
singing hymns of praise as she steps
她走的时候唱着赞美的赞美诗
into heaven what a wonderful wonderful
进入天堂是多么美好的奇妙
glorification and her her desire and
美化和她的欲望和
great prayer was through her death her
伟大的祈祷是通过她的死亡她
husband would come to Christ her
丈夫会来基督她
children would come to Christ and they
孩子们会来基督和他们
later did so God is glorified sometimes
后来这样做了上帝有时得到了荣耀
in taking us home sometimes that happens
有时会把我们带回家
in Exodus chapter 4 in verse 11 it says
在出埃及记4章第11节中说道
and the Lord said to Moses who has made
耶和华对摩西说谁取得了
man's mouth or who makes him dumb or
男人的嘴或谁使他愚蠢或
death or seeing or blind is it not I the
死亡或看见或失明不是我的
Lord it's God who does those things
主啊，上帝是做那些事的
that's not Satan it's God who does those
那不是撒旦是上帝做那些
things who is it that does that
是那样做的事情
now the question then comes what are
现在问题是什么呢
your responses to what's going on in
你对正在发生的事情的回应
life that's a key thing because our
生活是关键， 因为我们的生活
responses to life can produce sickness
对生活的反应会产生疾病
in our lives God created our bodies with
在我们的生活中，上帝创造了我们的身体
certain control mechanisms we have
我们拥有某些控制机制
automatic systems that go on within the
内部的自动系统
body hormones that work essentially on a
体内激素主要起作用
on a basis of supply and demand
供给和需求的基础上，
hormones these are combinations
荷尔蒙这些是组合
it's that supply and demand that really
这真的是供求关系
makes those hormones function there are
使那些荷尔蒙功能有所作为
combinations of blinking and breathing
眨眼和呼吸的组合
that are automatic but in some cases
这是自动的，但在某些情况下
actually can be controlled a bit there's
实际上可以控制一下
certain automatic reflexes that you have
你有一些自动反应
in your body as well to certain things
在你的身体以及某些事情
that happen for example if you were in a
这种情况发生，例如，如果 你在一个
dark room and all of a sudden somebody
黑暗的房间，突然有人
turned on a bright light you would
你想要一个明亮的灯光
automatically Britt blink without
自动布里特眨眼没有
thinking you don't have to go out when
以为你不必出门的时候
you go to a exercise class or you go out
你去参加一个运动课，或者你出去
running or you're exerting some egg you
跑步或者你正在施放一些鸡蛋
don't have to go out and deliberately
不必故意外出
think okay heart and respiratory
想好心脏和呼吸
respiration system I want you to I want
呼吸系统我想要你我想要的
the heart to beat more to supply more
更多的心脏打败更多
oxidant no no you have to do that it
氧化剂不，你不必这样做
just automatically happens those are all
只是自动发生这些都是
automatic controls that increase your
自动控制，增加你的
breathing and increase your heart rates
呼吸，增加心率
in order to supply oxygen and other
为了供应氧气等
needed elements to the rest of your body
你身体其他部分需要的元素
so and there are certain stimuli that
所以也有一定的刺激
produced specific effects you can touch
产生了你可以触摸的特定效果
an electric fence and all of a sudden
一个电围栏，突然间
your muscles immediately react to that
你的肌肉会立即做出反应
so certain stimuli produces specific
所以某些刺激产生特定的
results and some of these controls that
结果和其中一些控件
are automatic can actually be influenced
自动实际上可以受到影响
by our responses to life and problems in
通过我们对生活和问题的回应
life this gives you a little bit of
生活这给你的一点点
illustration this may be I don't know
插图这可能是我不知道的
this meet yeah I think it did make it
这是相遇的，我认为它确实成功了
into your notes but it made me not be
到你的笔记，但它让我不
very clear the body is divided down you
非常清楚身体被分割下来
see on the left hand side the
看左边的那个
parasympathetic system and sympathetic
副交感神经系统和交感神经
system all that is part of the autonomic
系统都是自主的一部分
nervous system the parasympathetic
神经系统副交感神经
system is essentially when your body is
系统基本上是你的身体
relaxed what happens will it constricts
放松会发生什么事情会收缩
your pupil it stimulates salivation
你的瞳孔刺激流涎
it constricts your bronchial area
它会收缩你的支气管区域
because you don't need as much oxygen or
因为你不需要那么多的氧气或
volume of oxygen going into your body it
氧气的体积进入你的 身体
stimulates activity and your digestive
刺激活动和消化
system stimulates your gallbladder
系统刺激你的胆囊
constricts your bladder it's a reason
收缩你的膀胱是一个原因
why and when you're really relaxed you
为什么以及何时你真的放松了
feel like using the restroom and it
感觉就像使用洗手间一样
stimulates sexual structures it's a
刺激性结构这是一个
reason why you counsel a young man
为什么你劝告一个年轻人
that's having problems with sexual
有性问题
desires and you say to him go out and
欲望，你对他说出去
run three miles why because that's when
跑三英里为什么因为那时候
the sympathetic system of the body takes
身体的交感神经系统需要
over and it helps to reduce that let's
结束，它有助于减少那个让我们
go over to the sympathetic side when
去到交感神经侧时
you're getting your body ready for
你准备好了你的身体
action or some kind of strenuous
行动还是某种费劲的
exercise it dilates the pupil and
锻炼它可以扩大瞳孔和瞳孔
inhibits salivation you're not thinking
抑制你不想的流涎
about eating so much accelerates your
关于吃这么多加速你的
heart rate right there it relaxes your
心率就在那里放松你的心
blonk bronchial area so that you can
支气管区域让你可以
suck in greater volume of air and
吮吸更多的空气和
inhibits activities in your digestive
抑制消化系统中的活动
system stimulates glucose release
系统刺激葡萄糖释放
there's a secretion of adrenaline and
肾上腺素和肾上腺素分泌
noradrenaline in the body relaxes your
体内的去甲肾上腺素可以放松身心
bladder and inhibit sexual structures
膀胱和抑制性结构
that's when you're ready to go that's
这是当你准备去那
the way God's designed us that's all of
上帝为我们设计的方式就是全部
those controls everything you see there
那些控制你在那里看到的一切
on the parasympathetic side the
在副交感神经方面
sympathetic side can be influenced by
交感神经侧可以通过影响
your responses to life how you're
你对生活的回应你是怎样的
dealing with life how you deal with
处理生活你如何处理
stress or the news that you're out of
压力或者你出的消息
money and you still have to pay the rent
钱，你仍然需要支付租金
how do you deal with that stress
你是如何应对这种压力的？
and that those responses to life can
那些对生活的反应可以
produce actual physical symptoms where
产生实际的身体症状
you start to think about something
你开始思考一些事情
that's really worrying you and you can
这真的让你很担心，你可以
almost feel your heart
几乎感觉到你的心
start to pump well you're not getting
开始抽水你没得到
ready for any activity or you
准备好任何活动或你
internalize that stress deep down inside
内心深处压力
and essentially your bowels are a
基本上你的肠子是一个
cross-section of muscles and you
肌肉和你的横截面
internalize that and it tenses up the
将其内化并使其紧随其后
bowels and you can get a spastic colon
肠子，你可以得到一个痉挛性结肠
from those things
从那些事情
there's nothing physiologically wrong
生理上没有任何错误
with you there's nothing physically
和你在一起没有任何身体上的东西
wrong with you but because you've
你错了，但因为你
internalized that stress those muscles
内化，压力那些肌肉
begin to contract and they do so so much
开始收缩，他们这么做
and they carry that muscle memory in
他们带着肌肉记忆
them that you can be at different places
他们，你可以在不同的地方
and automatically now your muscles in
并自动现在你的肌肉
your colon is now contracting and this
你的结肠正在收缩，这个
is what they call a spastic colon all
他们称之为痉挛性结肠
that is not a result of any kind of
这不是任何形式的结果
trigger physiological trigger in the
触发在生理触发器
body it's because you've internalized
因为你已经内化了
all this stress that's the way you deal
所有这些压力都是你处理的方式
with it on the outside you may look
你可以在外面看看它
perfectly calm everything's going great
完美平静一切都很美好
but on the inside you've internalized
但在内心你已经内化了
all of that and your muscles are
所有这些和你的肌肉都是
responding to it this is where the term
应对它，这是其中术语
psychosomatic comes from that is the way
心身来自于这种方式
that we think about our life cycle which
我们认为我们的生命周期，这
has to do with soul comes with a Greek
与灵魂有关的是希腊语
word suitcase o matic some Samata which
单词行李箱o matic一些Samata哪个
is a body
是一个身体
it's the souls effect upon the body or
这是灵魂对身体或身体的影响
how the mind thinks that affects the
思想是如何影响的
body actually psychosomatic is an old
身体实际上心身是一个古老的
term there's a newer term that tries to
术语有一个新的术语试图
express it psychoneuroimmunology is the
表达心理神经免疫学是
new term psychoneuroimmunology because
新一期精神神经免疫学因为
they realize it's a process of the
他们意识到这是的一个过程
neural system of the body and responses
身体的神经系统和反应
to life
生活
it can produce certain symptoms
它会产生某些症状
but does it have an organic cost no it
但它有没有它的有机成本
doesn't but though that internalized
虽然内化，但不是这样
stress has gone to your body to do that
压力已经到了你的身体去做
is training your body to respond to
训练你的身体回应
circumstances in your life like people
生活中的环境就像人一样
that have seemingly panic attacks that
那些看似惊慌失措的袭击事件
come out of nowhere we had a man in our
我们突然出现了一个男人
congregation had the worst panic attacks
会众遭受了最严重的恐慌袭击
of anybody I've ever seen
我所见过的任何人
he would have he'd be driving down a
他会有他会被拉低一个
freeway and have a panic attack it would
高速公路并且会发生惊恐发作
be all he could do to pull the car over
尽他所能把车拉过来
and he would literally sit on the side
他真的会站在一边
of the freeway with his hands frozen to
高速公路的双手冻得
the steering wheel of the car for hours
汽车的方向盘几个小时
until somebody came along and peeled his
直到有人出现并剥去他的
fingers away from it and picked him up
手指远离它并把他抱起来
physically out of the car and put him in
身体离开车并把他放进去
another car and took a moment that if he
另一辆车，花了一点时间，如果他
didn't show up after a period of time
一段时间后没出现
she called people to have him go out and
她叫人们让他出去
look for him he's sitting his side of
找他，他正坐在他的侧
the road frozen the steering wheel pain
道路冻结了方向盘的痛苦
attacks that seemingly come out of
似乎是出来的攻击
nowhere where you can be walking through
无处在这里你可以行走
a grocery store and there's no threat
一家杂货店，有没有威胁
there's no threat in your environment
你的环境没有威胁
whatsoever and all of a sudden you feel
无论如何，你突然感觉到了什么
your heart starting to race and and
你的心开始比赛和
there's nothing threatening in your
你的任何事都没有威胁
environment at all and you and the
环境，你和你
tendency is to think what's a
倾向是认为什么是
physiological I mean there was nothing
生理学我的意思是什么也没有
so I think environment when the trigger
所以我认为环境触发时
really comes from your soul your mind
真的来自你的灵魂你的思想
and your body's been trained to that and
和你的身体一直在训练这一点，
trained did that trigger now there are
现在已经训练了那个触发器
actual physiological problems that can
可以的实际生理问题
cause panic like attacks but those are
引起恐慌般的攻击，但那些是
correctable through surgery but most
通过手术可以纠正， 但大多数
panic attacks are not caused by a
惊恐发作不是由a引起的
physical problem they're caused by how a
身体问题他们是由如何造成的
person processes life so it's
人处理生活所以它是
interesting here what about the
这里有趣的是什么
frequency of these things well what is
这些事情的频率是 多少
interesting is 30 to 50 percent of
有趣的是 30％到50％
patients seen by the average primary
患者看到的平均原发性
care physician have physical symptoms
护理医师有身体症状
with no organic cause now I don't say
没有有机原因现在我不说
that
那
medical textbooks say that 30 to 50% of
医学教科书说30 ％到50％
patients seeing the average primary care
患者看到平均初级保健
physician have physical symptoms with no
医生有身体症状没有
organic costs Wow gastroenterologist
有机成本哇胃肠病学家
say that 40 percent of people who have
说有40％的人拥有
functional bowel syndrome have physical
功能性肠综合征有体质
symptoms with no organic cause that
症状没有有机原因
would mean that 40 percent of the people
将意味着40％的人
that see a gastroenterologist have
看到胃肠病学家了
spiritual problems going on that's
精神问题回事这是
causing physical problems the cause is
引起身体问题的原因是
physical I mean spiritual and the way
身体我的意思是精神和方式
that you respond to certain things in
你回应某些事情
life may aggravate diseases that are
生活可能会加剧疾病
already present 25 to 30% of patients
已经有25％至30％的患者出现
they say that's true you have already a
他们说这是真的，你已经有了
pre-existing disease or problem and now
现有的疾病或问题
your responses or your poor responses to
你的回答或你的反应不佳
life or unbiblical responses to life now
现在的生活或对生活的不符合圣经的反应
are just compounding those problems
正在加剧这些问题
physically medical treatment then you
然后你接受身体治疗
take medicine but that just slows down
吃药，但这只是放慢速度
the brain stimulus to the organ and at
对器官和大脑的大脑刺激
this particular point a placebo effect
这个特殊点是一种安慰剂效应
is very very evident and it's very
是非常非常明显的，这是非常
revealing in this particular case the
揭示了这个特殊情况
problem is not your problem it's your
问题不是你的问题，这是你的问题
response to the problems of life that is
回应生活中的问题
really the problem how am i responding
真的是问题我如何回应
to things in my life how am i processing
在我生命中的事情我如何处理
things in life you've ever been in a
生活中的事，你曾经去过的
situation where you really didn't like
你真的不喜欢的情况
going there but you had to maybe it's
去那里，但你不得不这样做
your job you don't really like going
你的工作你不喜欢去
there you say and you come home and say
在那里你说，你回家说
to your wife you know every time I go
你的 妻子，你知道我每次去
there I get sick there's nothing there
在那里我生病了那里什么都没有
that causes sickness it's just your your
导致疾病的只是你的
thinking and I just every time I go
想着，我只是我每次去
there I just feel sick to my stomach
在那里， 我只是感到恶心
as soon as I walk away I'm fine I walk
我一走开就走 ，我走得很好
back
背部
it's got to be in the air can't be me no
它必须在空中不能不是我
no no jus FEX how you feel how you
不，没有jus FEX你怎么感觉你
respond to life you can't necessarily
回应生活你不一定
change your circumstances but you can
改变你的情况，但你可以
change your response to your
改变你对你的回应
circumstances that's so critical your
对你来说如此重要的情况
response to those circumstances that's
回应那些情况
vitally important to understand so how
了解如何非常重要
are you responding to the adverse
你应对不利
circumstances that are going on in your
在即将于环境的
life well that's a good question which
生活很好，这是一个很好的问题
brings us to our next issue how do I
把我们带到下一期我怎么做
respond to it well then we have to
它反应良好 ， 那么我们就必须
evaluate it from the reasons that we're
从我们的原因评估它
given is it sin engendered is that the
给出的是它产生的罪是那个
problem have I had a poor discipline or
问题是我的纪律不好或者
a poor stewardship of my body I've
我的身体的一个贫穷的领导我已经
developed some sinful habits in my body
在我的身体里养成了一些罪恶的习惯
that have brought about autonomic like
这带来了自主的喜欢
responses I've trained the muscles on my
回应我训练的肌肉我
body to respond to stressful situations
身体应对压力的情况
so that they react this way what's
这样他们就会以这种方式做出反应
what's happening or is this problem that
发生了什么或是这个问题
I'm experiencing there in order to
我正在那里体验
prevent further sin in my life is that
防止进一步的罪恶在我生命中是
it
它
maybe it's dealing with my pride I
也许它正在处理我的骄傲我
always pride myself and being rather
总是为自己感到自豪， 而且很自负
healthy
健康
well maybe it's my pride and it's also
也许这是我的骄傲，也是
something that you need to pray about
你需要祈祷的东西
and really commit to Christ or is this
并真正承诺基督或是这样
there to glorify God can I die with
在那里荣耀上帝我能死吗？
God's grace trusting God all the way
上帝的恩典信靠神一路
through the illness right to the very
通过疾病权利到极了
end is that possible
结束是可能的
and how can this illness be used in
以及如何使用这种疾病
order to glorify God
为了荣耀上帝
we've got to recognize the truth of John
我们必须认识到约翰的真相
nine three that some illnesses are there
九点三，那里有一些疾病
what glorifies God ultimately is what is
最终荣耀上帝的是什么
best for the sick person and yet a lot
最适合病人而且很多
of people will do anything they can for
人会尽其所能 为
a cure
治愈
they're on a hunt to find testimonials
他们正在寻找推荐书
of past possible cures multiple
过去可能治愈多个
sclerosis my sister is a is a research
我妹妹硬化是一项研究
nurse for the Mayo Clinic in Phoenix
凤凰城梅奥诊所的护士
Arizona and she works in the area of
亚利桑那州和她在该地区工作
multiple sclerosis they're testing out
他们正在测试多发性硬化症
all kinds of things to see what's best
各种各样的事情，看看什么是最好的
type of treatment and the newer drugs
治疗类型和新药
that are coming along and sometimes she
即将到来，有时她
keeps me up on all the different stuff
让我了解所有不同的东西
that's going on in the MS area so let's
这是在MS区域进行的，所以让我们来吧
say for instance you have multiple
比方说你有多个
sclerosis there there's no known cure
硬化有没有已知的 治疗
for that particular disease but people
对于那种疾病，但人
will try and take every potential test
将尝试并采取所有潜在的测试
drug every potential vitam vitamin in
药物中每种潜在的维生素维生素
order to find a possible cure they'll
为了找到可能的治疗方法，他们会
they'll go all over the earth they'll
他们会到地球上去
hear about some remote testimony of some
听到一些远程证词
Amazon jungle tribe that has no
亚马逊丛林部落没有
occurrences of multiple sclerosis and
发生多发性硬化症
they'll move there and start eating
他们会搬到那里开始进食
their diet you know they'll do weird
他们的饮食你知道他们会做的很奇怪
bizarre things as if all we have is the
奇怪的事情好像我们拥有的一切都是
here and now oh they could be spending
在这里，现在哦，他们可以花钱
their latter days on earth making things
他们后来在地球上制造东西
right with family members learning to
与家人学习的权利
glorify God in those ways listen here's
通过这些方式来荣耀上帝
the good news we're all gonna die that's
好消息我们都会死的
the good news I'll get to be with my
我会得到的好消息
Savior that's the good news
救主这是个好消息
we're all gonna die that's why I tell
我们都会死，这就是我说的原因
the medical doctors in our in our church
我们教会里的医生
I say to them Wow I would you you have
我告诉他们哇我想你
got to work in one of the most
得到了最多的工作之一
depressing situations of any job because
压抑任何工作的情况，因为
you're gonna fail 100% of the
你会失败100％的失败
time every single one of your patients
时间每一位患者
are gonna die eventually how would you
最终会死的你会怎么样？
like to work in a job where you failed
喜欢在失败的工作中工作
100% of the time
100％的时间
Oh that'd be really discouraging so
噢， 那会非常沮丧如此
that's why people are we're gonna die
这就是为什么 人们我们是怎么死的
that that's the way it is so I want to
这就是我想要的方式
die as best as possible to glorify God
尽可能地死去荣耀上帝
in that way when I was in South Africa
就在那时我在南非
back a few years ago I met with a or
倒退几年前，我遇到了一个或
there was about a hundred black pastors
那里有大约一百名黑人牧师
that had come out of the bush and we had
那是从 灌木丛中 走出来的
a Q&A session I'll never forget one of
一个Q＆A 会议我永远不会忘记其中一个
those dear elderly black pastors raise
那些亲爱的老黑人牧师提出来
his hand he says what do you do if you
他说，如果你，你会怎么做
have a congregation of 400 people and
有400人众，
you know in the next five years almost
你知道在接下来的五年里差不多了
all of them are gonna be gone they're
所有这些都将会消失
gonna be dead I never thought about that
会死的我从来没有想过这个
I thought wow
我觉得哇
you probably could answer this better
你可能会更好地回答这个问题
than I could I but I thought about a
我可以，但我想到了
little bit and I said to him well I
一点点，我 很好地对他说
guess I would spend my time teaching
我想我会花时间教学
them how to die well how did I see the
他们怎么样死得很好我怎么看
AIDS epidemic has really swept through
艾滋病疫情确实席卷而来
and and they're coming out of the tribal
并且他们从部落出来了
system and what the news doesn't tell
系统和新闻没有说明什么
you is that polygamy is what's really
你是一夫多妻制是什么是真正的
causing the AIDS epidemic to really
真正导致艾滋病流行
swell because you've got one man and
因为你有一个男人和男人， 所以会膨胀
he's got 14 wives and usually if he has
他有14个妻子，如果有的话
AIDS then the rest of his wives have
艾滋病然后其余的妻子都有
aged but they don't want to the
年龄，但他们不希望将
sociologists don't want to mess with the
社会学家不想搞砸了
tribal system and mess up the polygamy
部落制度和搞乱一夫多妻制
that goes on there so they don't talk
那就在那里，所以他们不说话
about that at all but that's the thing
关于那个，但那是事情
that's killing them I don't want to talk
那杀了他们我不想说话
about that kind of thing so what do you
关于那种事情你呢？
do if you minister in that kind of
如果你在那种方面服事呢？
environment that's really a death
环境真的是一个死亡
environment everybody in your
环境中的每个人
congregation is going to be gone in the
众会在被消失
next four or five years well if I'm
接下来的四五年如果我好的话
going to pass our congregation like that
要像那样通过我们的会众
we're all going to learn how to die well
我们都将学会如何度过难关
we're all going to learn how to die to
我们都将学会如何去死
the honor and glory of the Lord Jesus
主耶稣的荣耀和荣耀
Christ
基督
got to do that so you have to recognize
必须这样做，所以你必须认识到
the truth of John 9 3 you have to
约翰福音93的真相你必须这样做
evaluate your personal goals in life
评估你的人生目标
what are your personal goal
你的个人目标是什么？
what is really most important to you
对你来说最重要的是什么
again what glorifies God is best for the
再一次荣耀上帝是最好的
sick person is that is it your goal to
病人是你的目标
get well or is it your goal to glorify
康复还是你的目标是荣耀
God Luke chapter 10 Mary and Martha you
神卢克第10章玛丽和玛莎你
know that story
知道那个故事
Martha was busy with the things of this
玛莎忙于处理这件事
life Jesus says that's the way a lot of
生活耶稣说这是很多的方式
people are who are sick they're busy
人是谁生病 他们正忙
with the things of this life that means
用这生命中的事物意味着
that's their focus John 4:34 my food is
这是他们的焦点约翰福音4:34 我的食物是
to do the will of him who sent me and to
做他的意愿，谁送我和
accomplish his work jesus said that
完成他的工作，耶稣说，
should be our will first Timothy 4:7 on
应该是我们的第一个提摩太前书4：7
the other hand discipline yourself for
另一方面训练自己
the purpose of godliness so you get all
敬虔的目的，所以你得到了所有
of these passages that are really
这些段落真的是
critical I love what joe 2:10 says in
我很喜欢乔2:10所说的
fact back in 1985 when my father was
事实上早在1985年我的父亲就是
dying of my load of lastic syndrome
死于我的乳腺综合症
which is a form of leukemia he could
这是白血病的一种形式，他可以
tell I wasn't taking his death well he
告诉我没有服用他去世以及他
looked up from his bed and he said to me
他从床上抬起头来对我说
John shall we accept good from God and
约翰，我们就要接受上帝和好
not trouble those are the words of job
不要麻烦那些是工作的话
to his wife right whoa are we gonna say
他的妻子，我们要说谁
we're gonna be Fairweather Christians
我们将成为Fairweather基督徒
and say Lord as long as you see send
只要你看到发送 ，就说主
good things my way everything's gonna be
好事我的方式一切都会好起来的
great but the moment you allow bad
伟大，但 你允许坏的那一刻
things to come into my life all bets are
所有投注都将进入我的生活
off
离
that's Fairweather Christianity it's not
这是Fairweather基督教不是
real Christianity at all job 210 or the
真正的基督教在所有工作210或
remarkable statement by Joseph there in
由约瑟夫显着的声明中有
Genesis 50:20 - its brothers right after
创世纪50:20 -其兄弟紧随其后
all they had done to him robbed him of
他们对他所做的一切都抢走了他
his teenage years with his father he
他和父亲一起度过了十几岁的孩子
says to them now he's got power over
现在告诉他们他已经掌权了
them as a leader in Egypt he says to
他说，他们是埃及的领导者
them shall we except you intended all
我们除了你打算全部以外我们
this for evil but God intended it for
这是为了邪恶， 但上帝打算这样做
good the saving of many lives you
很好地拯救了你的许多生命
intended all this for evil
意图这一切都是为了邪恶
God always promises that his will will
上帝总是承诺他的意志会
be glorified in our lives he doesn't
在我们的生活中得到荣耀 他没有
necessarily promise deliverance funny
必然承诺拯救有趣
story of Johnny Erickson tada and John
Johnny Erickson tada和John的故事
McArthur interesting story after John
麦克阿瑟在约翰之后的有趣故事
MacArthur had carried her up several
麦克阿瑟带了她好几个
years ago this happened a flight of
年前，这件事发生 的飞行
stairs he put her in a wheelchair but in
楼梯他把她放在轮椅上，但在
the process of doing so he lost his belt
这样做的过程他失去了腰带
and balance and fell on her arm well she
并且平衡并且很好地落在她的手臂上
can't feel her arm obviously she said
她说，显然感觉不到她的手臂
Wow she said I'll bet that hurt God had
哇，她说我敢打赌上帝受伤了
brought her from a standpoint of
从一个角度来看她
accepting her quadriplegic state to
接受她的四肢瘫痪状态
actually embracing it
实际上拥抱它
she'd embraced it she could actually
她实际上已经接受了它
joke about it wonder how many of us
关于它的笑话让我们感到惊讶
could do that I'll bet that hurt well
可以这样做我敢打赌那伤害很好
you can see here then as well that
你可以在这看到那个
you've got to be responsible no matter
无论如何，你必须要负责任
how you feel
你的感受
no how matter how you feel you have a
不管你觉得自己怎么样
disease then what does God want you to
那么疾病就是上帝要你的
do about it are you upset are you angry
怎么办呢，你不高兴你生气
how are you processing that particular
你是如何处理这个特殊的
problem what if you have something that
问题如果你有什么东西
medicine has not discovered yet then God
医学还没有发现上帝
has a purpose in that too we still have
有一个目的，我们仍然有
a responsibility to obey Him and as a
有责任服从他和作为一个人
good steward we're not gonna spend all
好管家，我们不会花光所有
of our time and money trying to find
我的时间和金钱试图找到
some kind of cure
某种治疗方法
and yet that's exactly what a lot of
然而这正是很多东西
people do I love to ask counsel these
人们，我喜欢向 这些人 提出建议
three questions at this particular point
在这一点上有三个问题
question number one is could God have
第一个问题是上帝能做到的
stopped this and the answer is always
停止了这个，答案总是如此
what yes yes he could have question
是的，他可以提问
number two
第二
didy the office answer is no he could
didy办公室答案是否定的，他可以
have but he didn't question number three
但他没有质疑第三
then what is God's purpose in this what
那么上帝的目的是什么呢？
is God's purpose in this God have
是上帝在这个上帝的目的
stopped this whatever disease whatever
无论什么疾病，这都会阻止
problem you have yes did he know then
他有问题，是的，他当时就知道了
what is God's purpose in you having this
你有这个，上帝的目的是什么？
disease there is a divine purpose in
疾病有一个神圣的目的
this again God's purposes is far more
这又是上帝的目的更多
than just getting the sick person well
而不仅仅是让病人好
say oK we've talked about all these
说oK我们已经谈到了所有这些
physical disease you've talked about
你谈过的身体疾病
sicknesses and all this stuff but what
疾病和所有这些东西，但是什么
about stuff like chemical imbalances
关于化学不平衡等问题
what about that well let's talk about
那么好吧，让我们来谈谈
that there are specific medical issues
有具体的医疗问题
here that are important now a chemical
这里现在重要的是化学品
imbalance this is gives you a little bit
不平衡这给你一点点
of an example here of neurons in the
这里的神经元的一个例子
brain and neuron is if fascinating cell
大脑和神经元是迷人的细胞
the body unlike all the other cells of
身体不同于所有其他细胞
your body like a liver cell or a cell
你的身体像肝细胞或细胞
and your kidneys or a cell at the end of
和你的肾脏或细胞结束
your big toe these particular cells have
你的大脚趾这些特殊的细胞有
the capacity to carry on constant
能够继续进行
communication with one another one
彼此一个通信
neuron can carry over a thousand
神经元可以携带超过一千
different conversations with nearby
与附近的不同对话
neurons at the same time now I know some
同时神经元现在我知道一些
of you are good at talking but try to do
你擅长说话，但试着去做
that carry on simultaneous a thousand
同时进行一千个
different conversations
不同的对话
that's one neuron in your brain and you
这是你脑中的一个神经元和你
oh you have almost a hundred billion of
哦，你有近千亿美元
them in your brain that rivals the
他们在你的大脑中可以媲美
number of stars in the Milky Way the
在银河系恒星数量
brain is probably the most complex thing
大脑可能是最复杂的事情
that we know in our organic and physical
我们在有机和物质方面都知道
environment it's unbelievable
环境令人难以置信
makes you think there's a God there
让你觉得那里有一位上帝
and it's comprised of all these neurons
它由所有这些神经元组成
and these neurons have axons and
这些神经元有轴突和
dendrites axons are those little
树突轴突是那些小的
tentacles that grow out from your
从你的长出来的触手
neurons that carry messages away from
携带信息的神经元
the neuron dindt rights are the tenant
神经元dindt权利是租户
chemical or little tentacles that carry
化学或小触手携带
the message into the neuron and there's
进入神经元的信息就在那里
a little space between the end of an
结束之间的一点空间
axon and a and the beginning of a dent
轴突和a和凹痕的开始
right called the synaptic cleft and
右边称为突触间隙和
there's a chemical in that little space
那个小空间里有一种化学物质
there's little chemicals that are sent
发送的化学物质很少
from the end of that axon and if you
从那个轴突的末端，如果你
were to blow this up and I think there's
要把它炸掉，我想是的
an example of it there in your notes it
在你的笔记中有一个例子
would look something like this there's
会看起来像这样的东西
little chemicals at the end of the axon
轴突末端的少量化学物质
that are known as serotonin
被称为5-羟色胺
norepinephrine dopamine and in that
去甲肾上腺素多巴胺就在那里
little space in between and that
两者之间的空间很小
synaptic cleft
突触间隙
there is another chemical called MA
还有一种名为MA的化学物质
known a mean oxidase and that little
已知平均氧化酶而且很少
chemical sort of acts like the theory is
化学类似于理论的行为
and chemical imbalances a killer whale
和化学物质失衡是一种虎鲸
that comes along and consumes all the
它来了并消耗所有
neurofen Efrain or the serotonin that's
神经纤维Efrain或血清素
community or the dopamine that's
社区或多巴胺
communicated from the axon of one neuron
从一个神经元的轴突传达
to the dendrite of another neuron goes
对另一个神经元的树突去了
around and consumes it absorbs it when
周围消耗它吸收它时
that particular process is interrupted
那个特定的过程被打断了
this is what they theorize nobody knows
这是他们理论上没人知道的
exactly for sure that's the process that
确切地说，这是一个过程
they theorize occurs in chemical
他们理论上发生在化学上
imbalances and so that's the reason why
失衡，所以这就是为什么
they give antidepressants to people who
他们给那些服用抗抑郁药的人服用抗抑郁药
supposedly have this chemical imbalance
据说有这种化学不平衡
in order to the selective serotonin
为了选择性5-羟色胺
reuptake inhibitors in order to
再摄取抑制剂以便
encourage a better communication or
鼓励更好的沟通或
connection between those axons and
这些轴突和之间的联系
dendrites and now all my neurons you'll
树突，现在我所有的神经元
hear people say are firing that means
听到有人说这是开枪的意思
are all connecting all the messages are
都是连接所有消息的
coming together and the theory is the
走到一起，理论是
reason why people who are depressed are
为什么郁闷的人是
confused they can't focus they can't
困惑他们无法专注他们不能
concentrate is that there's that
专注是那就是
interruption that's going on there but
正在那里发生的中断但是
in fact here's a good illustration of
事实上， 这是一个很好的例子
this Pfizer illustration neurons have
这个辉瑞的插图神经元有
specialized projection called dendrites
称为树突的专门投影
and axon dendrites bring information to
和轴突树突带来的信息
the neuron cell body and axons take
神经元细胞体和轴突
information away from the neuron cell
信息远离神经元细胞
body incoming information is received by
收到身体传入的信息
the dendrites and passes through the
通过树突和通行证
neuron cell body and through the axon of
神经元细胞体和通过轴突
the neuron for communication between
神经元之间的沟通
neurons to occur an electrical impulse
神经元发生电脉冲
must travel down the axon to the
必须沿着轴突向下行进
synaptic terminal the problem with that
突触终端的问题
is most researchers now say that's very
大多数研究人员现在说的非常
simplistic you'll hear still you'll hear
简单的你会听到你仍然会听到
pop psychologists and you'll hear a lot
流行心理学家，你会听到很多
of people and even a lot of Christians
人，甚至很多基督徒
talk about chemical imbalances but most
谈论化学失衡，但大多数
researchers now are saying chemical
研究人员现在说化学品
imbalances is a very very poor way of
失衡是非常非常差的方式
describing it it's a very simplistic way
描述它是一种非常简单的方式
they think that the reason why people
他们认为人之所以如此
have phobias and the reason people
有恐惧症和人的原因
struggle with depression is because of
与抑郁症斗争是因为
the limbic brain the olymbia brain
边缘大脑是olymbia大脑
essentially is the hypothalamus they and
基本上是 他们和他们 的下丘脑
the amygdala are two parts of the brain
杏仁核是大脑的两个部分
that many believe are implicated in
许多人认为有牵连
depressive and anxiety disorders why do
抑郁和焦虑症为何如此
they think that well it's small areas of
他们认为这是小范围的
the brain the hypothalamus governs first
大脑下丘脑支配第一
appetite sleep pleasure sexual desire
食欲睡眠快感性欲
and aggression those are the body's
和侵略这些是身体的
functions that are most affected in
受影响最大的功能
depression so they think it's not really
抑郁， 所以他们认为这不是真的
a neuron issue anymore the real more
一个神经元问题不再是真正的问题
popular idea is it's a malfunction of
流行的观点是它的故障
the hypothalamus which governs all this
治疗这一切的下丘脑
areas because when a person becomes
区域，因为当一个人成为
depressed either they don't have any
郁闷要么他们没有
thirst or they have a lot of thirst or
口渴或他们有很多口渴或
they don't have any appetite or they
他们没有胃口或他们
have a lot of appetite or they don't
有很多胃口或他们没有
sleep well or they don't experience much
睡得好或者他们没有多少经历
pleasure they don't have much sexual
他们没有多少性欲
desire or they have way too much sexual
欲望或他们有太多性
desire or they're not they're very
欲望或他们不是他们非常
passive or they're extremely
被动或他们非常
aggressive so that seems to be extremes
积极因此似乎是极端的
that are governed by the hypothalamus
由下丘脑支配
the Mignola is another part it's
米尼奥拉是另一个部分
believed that it controls the brain's
相信它控制着大脑
ability to react in fear which is
在恐惧这是反应的能力
implicated in anxiety disorders so when
牵连焦虑症，所以当
a person has a panic attack then that
一个人有恐慌症发作那么
would essentially be a part of the
基本上是一部分
amygdala the amygdala malfunctions for
amygdala amygdala故障
some reason but again nobody knows for
某种原因，但没有人知道
for sure absolutely so there's still a
可以肯定绝对所以还是有
lot of debate on why do these things
很多 关于为什么做这些事情的辩论
really happen it's almost as if in order
真的发生了它几乎就像是有序的
to find out for sure you'd have to kill
要确定你必须杀死
the patient to find out whether what's
病人要知道是否是什么
really causing their depression but as
真的导致他们的抑郁，但是
soon as you do that then you lose the
你这么做就会失败
opportunity to tell what's really
有机会说出真的
causing the depression now regardless of
现在无论如何都会 导致抑郁
what happens here or what they
这里发生了什么或他们是什么
ultimately conclude the question is
最终得出结论的问题是
which came first depression or the
这是第一次沮丧或
imbalance now I want you to notice what
不平衡现在我想让你注意到什么
the Bible says and answer that question
圣经上说，回答这个问题
take your Bible just for a moment let's
把你的圣经只是片刻，让我们
go over to proverbs 14 and verse 30
转到箴言14和30节
proverbs chapter 14 and verse 30 a
谚语第14章和第30节a
tranquil heart is life to the body but
宁静的心脏是生命的身体，但
passion is rottenness to the bone the
激情是腐朽的骨头
Hebrew word for passion here is a word
这里充满希伯来语的热情是一句话
that can be in it could be translated of
可以在 它可以转化的
the ideas internal turmoil you know her
你认识她的内心动荡的想法
upset sometimes we say internal passion
有时候我们会说内心激情
upset internal turmoil but passion is
心烦意乱的内部动荡，但激情
rottenness to the bones is the idea or a
腐烂到骨头是想法或者
prowess chapter 15 and verse 30 bright
实力第15章和第30节明亮
eyes gladden the heart good news put fat
眼睛高兴的是心里的好消息
on the bones so how we process life in
在骨头上，我们如何处理生活
our spirit our soul and by the way there
我们的灵魂和我们的灵魂
is no distinction between spirit and
精神和精神没有区别
soul there are basically the immaterial
灵魂有基本上无关紧要
part of man when you study soul and
当你研究灵魂和灵魂时，你的一部分
spirit throughout the Bible the Spirit
整本圣经的精神精神
is that immaterial part of man out of
是人类的非物质部分
connection with the body the soul is
与 身体的灵魂，是 连接
that immaterial part of man in
人类无关紧要的一部分
connection with the body that's the
与身体的连接
distinction between the two but both of
区分两者但两者兼而有之
them refer
他们参考
to the immaterial part of man so when my
对我这个时代的非物质部分
soul is not processing things well then
灵魂不能很好地处理事情
it has effect upon my body
它对我的身体有影响
passion is rottenness to the bones or
激情是骨头或骨头的腐烂
proverbs chapter 17 and verse 22 a
谚语第17章和第22节a
joyful heart is good medicine but a
快乐的心是好药，但是
broken spirit dries up the bones that's
忧伤的灵枯竭，这是骨头
a person who's crushed to has no hope
谁是 压死一个人有没有希望
broken spirit oftentimes it's
经常破碎的精神
descriptive in old ancient hebrew
描述古老的希伯来语
terminology of a person who's really
一个人的术语真的
severely depressed tries to vote in
严重沮丧的人试图投票
other words it has an effect upon the
换句话说，它会影响到
physical health of the body we know that
我们知道人体的身体健康
a depressed person over a long period of
一个长期的抑郁的人
time that's chronically depressed it
多数民众赞成长期郁闷呢时间
suppresses the immune system and those
抑制免疫系统和那些
people tend to be more sickly than other
人们往往比其他人病得更厉害
people we know that in fact that part is
我们知道的人实际上那部分是
measurable and the Bible confirms that
可衡量的，圣经证实了这一点
the Bible says the spirits conditioned
圣经说精神有条件
the soul's condition has a huge effect
灵魂的状况产生了巨大的影响
on how the body responds to life
关于身体如何回应生活
circumstances well then the question
情况好然后问题
comes do drugs work well that's a great
药物运作良好，这是一个伟大的
question but you got to define what do
问题，但你必须定义做什么
you mean by work and this is where we
你的意思是工作， 这是我们的地方
get into the problem of the placebo
进入安慰剂的问题
effect I mentioned to you earlier in one
我之前提到的一个效果
of the sessions the st. John wort story
届圣 。约翰麦汁故事
about the work that had been done and
关于已完成的工作和
reported in the Journal of the American
在美国杂志上报道
Medical Association the st. John wort
医学会圣。约翰麦汁
study there is also a study that was
研究还存在，这是一个研究
done in the American Journal of
在美国的杂志上完成
Psychiatry on the functional anatomy of
精神病学对人体功能解剖学的影响
a placebo effect that asks this question
一个安慰剂效应，问这个问题
do placebos when they alleviate
做安慰剂，当他们减轻
depressive symptoms produce actual
抑郁症状产生实际
changes in the brain well the answer to
变化在大脑很好的答案
that study was a simple yes I'm not
那项研究很简单，我不是
going to go through all the statistics
要查看所有统计数据
of it but yes a placebo changes the
但它是一个安慰剂改变了
chemicals in a brain and then in study
大脑中的化学物质，然后在研究中
goes on and says
接着说
any kind of talk therapy they've been
他们去过的任何一种谈话疗法
able to measure also changes the
能够衡量也改变了
chemicals in the brain so the reality is
大脑中的化学物质就是现实
that placebos and talk therapies such as
那个安慰剂和谈话疗法如
biblical counseling also changes brain
圣经辅导也会改变大脑
chemistry in fact talk therapy gives a
化学实际上谈话治疗给了一个
person a new disposition a new view of
人新配置的新观点
life that actually changes the chemical
生活实际上改变了化学物质
components of the brain that's
大脑的组成部分
interesting and then the st. John wort
有趣，然后圣。约翰麦汁
study published in the Journal of the
研究发表在“华尔街日报”上
American Medical Association that
美国医学会认为
examines the effectiveness of placebos
检查安慰剂的有效性
to relieve depressive symptoms as
减轻抑郁症状
compared with other treatments for
与其他治疗方法相比
depression then this carefully designed
抑郁症然后这个精心设计
study 340 depressed men and women were
研究340抑郁的男性和女性
divided into three groups
分为三组
113 were given st. John wort which is a
给了113分。约翰麦汁是一个
natural medication given primarily for
天然药物主要用于治疗
depression 116 were given placebos 111
抑郁症116给予安慰剂111
were given Zoloft
给了Zoloft
which is of course a well-known
这当然是众所周知的
antidepressant and after eight weeks of
抗抑郁药和八周后
treatment all three groups improved with
治疗三组均有改善
no statistical difference among them all
他们之间没有统计差异
three groups improved now one single
现在三个小组改进了一个单一
study cannot establish the validity of
学习不能建立的有效性
an observation but according to the
的观察，但 根据
Journal of American Medical Association
美国医学会杂志
this study is not alone this is what
这项研究并不孤单，这是什么
they say let me quote JAMA for you and
他们说让我为你引用JAMA
they say an increasing number of studies
他们说越来越多的研究
have failed to show a difference between
未能显示出差异
active Anna depressants and a placebo
活跃的安娜抑郁症和安慰剂
end of quote page eighteen hundred and
引用页面的结尾一百八十和
thirteen did you hear what they said
十三，你听到了他们说的话
this is a journal the American Medical
这是美国医学杂志
Association an increasing number of
协会越来越多的
studies have failed to show any
研究未能显示任何
difference between an active an and a
活动an和a之间的区别
precedent of placebo so the placebo
安慰剂的先例，所以安慰剂
effect when it's in pill form is
药丸形式的效果是
increasing at a rate they go on to say
以他们继续说的速度增长
of about seven percent each decade in
每十年约七成
other words if 30% of the people of
换句话说，如果人民的 30％
depressed people responded to placebos
抑郁的人回应安慰剂
in nineteen
在十九岁
seventy fifty percent of that group
该组的百分之七十五
would respond to them today so we're
我们今天会回应他们，所以我们是
placing greater in its decade after
在之后的十年中取得更大的成就
decade goes by greater and greater trust
十年越来越多的信任
and medication to solve the problem such
和药物来解决这样的问题
you simply see both suggests that as a
你只是看到两者都表明这是一个
culture we're putting more and more hope
文化我们正在投入越来越多的希望
in our pills the placebo effect is a
在我们的药片安慰剂效应是
measure of our confidence the trust that
衡量我们对信任的信心
we place in a particular object those
我们把它放在一个特定的对象中
who put their trust in which doctors
谁信任哪位医生
might die from his voodoo threats
可能会死于他的伏都教威胁
because they believe in witch doctors
因为他们相信巫医
those who trust in pills might report
那些信任药片的人可能会报告
some healing from placebos because they
从安慰剂中得到一些治疗，因为他们
believe in the medication as long as
只要相信药物
psychiatric medications are perceived as
精神科药物被认为是
the deepest treatment for depression the
抑郁症的最深治疗方法
placebo effect will flourish whoa
安慰剂效应将蓬勃发展哇哇
it will flourish so do they work what do
它会蓬勃发展，所以他们的工作是做什么的
you mean by work if we're talking about
你的意思是工作，如果我们谈论
work in the sense of does it cure the
工作在它治愈的意义上
problem the organic disorder then it
问题有机失调那么它
doesn't work because as soon as the
不会因为工作不久的
medicine wears off the organic or the
药物磨损有机物或
problem is back most medications in
问题是回到大多数药物
order to work has to cure the problem it
为了工作必须解决它的问题
has to do that so there's no active
必须这样做，所以没有活跃
ingredients in a placebo things you have
你有安慰剂的成分
to consider is the patient the medical
考虑是病人的医疗
doctor or psychiatrist caring for the
医生或精神科医生照顾
patient and whether or not the patient
患者和患者是否
feels that they're being cared for the
觉得他们受到了照顾
environment makes a difference in the
环境有所不同
effects of the placebo as well all of
安慰剂的影响以及所有的安慰剂
these are key so what's really going on
这些是关键，所以真正发生了什么
you have problems that are going on in
你有问题正在发生
life you have certain responses to those
你对生活有一定的回应
but particular problems that maybe are
但可能是特别的问题
unbiblical thinking and poor attitudes
不符合圣经的思想和不良的态度
and those particular problems then
然后是那些特殊的问题
produce bad attitudes in your life which
在你的生活中产生不良的态度
slows the life down there's decreased
生命减慢，减少了
functioning which now just increases the
功能现在只是增加了
problems that are going on in your life
你生活中正在发生的 问题
and so what's often introduced to that
所以经常引入的是什么
is some kind of drug or a placebo effect
某种药物或安慰剂效应
and now I start to feel a lot better
现在我开始 感觉好多了
because I have a drug that helps me so I
因为我有一种药可以帮助我，所以我
feel better so it works
感觉更好，所以它有效
it helps me what do you mean
它对我有帮助你的意思
work well then here are some questions
工作得很好，这里有一些问题
to ask and this is often will give to
要问，这往往会给予
counsel EES who are seeing physicians
咨询医生的EES律师
who claim a physical problem like
谁声称身体问题像
chemical imbalance or maybe even if
化学不平衡甚至可能
they're really up on things there's a
他们真的很喜欢那里的东西
malfunction of the hypothalamus or the
下丘脑或故障
amygdala it's producing emotion or
杏仁核它产生情感或
behavior problems concerning the
有关的行为问题
diagnosis what tests were run to prove a
诊断运行什么测试以证明a
physical symptom is present
存在身体症状
that's question good question how do
那个问题好问题怎么做
these tests prove the presence of that
这些测试证明了存在
is the condition proven demonstratable
是证明可证明的条件
fact or simply a theory what about the
事实上或者简要 的 理论是什么
behavior well how do you know that the
行为好你怎么知道的
diagnosed physical problem is the cause
诊断出身体问题是原因
of the emotion or behavior or actions of
的情绪或行为或行为
the person is it is the link proven a
这个人是经过证明的链接
demonstratable fact or simply a theory
可证实的事实或简单的理论
concerning medication what proof do you
关于药物什么证明你
have that the medicine that you're
那是你的药
recommending corrects the physical
建议纠正物理
problem sometimes if it's only treating
问题有时如果它只是治疗
the symptoms it's like giving a person
它的症状就像给人一样
an anaesthetic who's sitting on a tack
一个坐在大头钉上的麻醉剂
they feel better say it's working the
他们觉得更好说它正在发挥作用
medicines working but as soon as the
药品工作，但只要
anesthetic wears off guess what ouch the
麻醉消退猜测哎哟的
tack is still there what do you mean at
大概仍然存在你的意思
work now you got to remember as a
工作现在你必须记住作为一个
counselor it's not our job to practice
辅导员这不是我们的工作
medicine you didn't put them on the
你没有把它们放在药上
medication and it's not your place to
药物治疗，这不是你的地方
take them off of it work with a medical
带他们离开它与医疗工作
physician not in place of one when a
医生不代替一个人
person is under care or the authority of
人受到照顾或权威
a medical doctor it's unethical to
一个医生，这是不道德的
overrule that authority especially in an
否定这种权威，特别是在一个
area where you're not trained however if
在那里你不但是如果训练的区域
a medical doctor is dedicated to
一位医生致力于
constantly frustrating or refuting the
经常令人沮丧或反驳
theological counselling that you're
你是神学辅导
giving to the council leave an area
给予该局离开一个区域
where he or she has little or no
他或她很少或没有的地方
training then make sure your council
培训然后确保你的理事会
ease finds a different doctor hopefully
容易找到一个不同的医生
a doctor that'll work with you and not
一个与你合作的医生，而不是
against you I remember several years ago
几年前 我还记得你
as a pastor back in the Ohio area we had
作为牧师回到我们在俄亥俄州的地区
a secular doctor who didn't buy into all
一个世俗的医生谁没买成所有
the psychobabble that
心理上的那种
out there and so I'd send all my counsel
在那里，所以我发送我的所有忠告
ease to him I'd say now you got to go on
缓解他我现在会说你得去上
witness to him and he loved it he loved
看到他， 他很喜欢 他爱
getting the patient's alright but he
让病人好，但他
didn't he wouldn't put him on heavy
不是他不会让他变得沉重
psychotropic drugs he let me work with
他让我和我一起工作的精神药物
them using good biblical help and then
他们使用良好的圣经帮助然后
at the same time he would treat their
同时他会对待他们的
actual physical problems you may have to
您可能需要的实际身体问题
find a physician that will work with you
找一位 能与你合作 的医生
and that in this area we've trained a
在这个领域，我们训练了一个
number of doctors through our graduate
通过我们的毕业生的医生数量
program biblical counseling after
程序后的圣经辅导
getting their doctorates and they've
获得他们的博士学位，他们已经
come to masters and a number of doctors
来到硕士和一些医生
and nurses all the way throughout the
护士一路贯穿
Southern California area so there you go
南加州地区所以你去
that's a quick overview to kind of help
这是一个快速概述的帮助
you with dealing with the physiological
你对付生理
problems
问题
you
您